CLARA PEÑALVA CARBONELL

València, Spain | clara.penyalva@gmail.com | mural.uv.es/clapecar

Professional Summary

Excellent academic record, with some experience in research and development projects. Knowledge of mathematics and physics, along with a creative basis, applied in different projects of animation and simulation. With desire to learn and improve.

Skills

- Ability to work under pressure
- Adaptability
- Creativity
- Fast learner
- Persistent
- Teamwork

- OS: Windows, Linux (Ubuntu, Fedora)
- Computer Languages: C++, C#, Python, Java, OpenGI/GLSL, SQL, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript
- Software:
 Blender, Microsoft Visual
 Studio, Unity, MatLab,
 SQL Developer, Gimp,
 Adobe Premiere

Education

Bachelor of Science: Degree in Multimedia Engineering [GPA 9.05 / 10] 09/2013 – 09/2017 **School of Engineering (ETSE)** - **University of Valencia** - Av. de l'Universitat, s/n, 46100 Burjassot, Spain

Extraordinary Bachelor's Degree award

I have developed several individual and team projects during my degree:

- Complete 3D platformer video game for PC using <u>Unity</u> and <u>C#</u>.
- Use of <u>Blender</u> software (<u>blender.org</u>), making <u>plug-ins</u> with <u>Python</u> and learning kinetic chains, IK, applied to different characters in animated short film (as a Computer Animation's final project). Processing MOCAP data files.
- Implementation of the models Smoothed Particle Hydrodynamics (<u>SPH</u>), Position Based Dynamics (<u>PBD</u>) and Position Based Fluids (<u>PBS</u>), using Processing (Java) and Unity 3D (C#).
- Simulation of <u>Soft Objects</u> based on mass-spring model and simulation of <u>ocean waves</u> using Processing (Java).
- Simulation of Steering Behaviours and Boids Flocking (AI).
- Implementation of $\underline{A^*}$ algorithm. Furthermore, I have introduced this into Steering Agents. Simulation of $\underline{Pathfinding}$.
- GPU programming with C ++, OpenGI/GLSL and OSG, using vertex, fragment, geometry, tessellation and compute $\underline{Shaders}$.

Work History

No doctor researcher

11/2017 - 7/2018

University Research Institute on Robotics and Information and Communication Technologies (IRTIC) - C/ Catedrático José Beltrán, 2, 46980 Paterna, Spain

University Research Institute on Robotics and Information and Communication Technologies (IRTIC), department LSyM.

Project: research and development of advanced technologies for simulation of port machinery.

Grant for the introduction to research

10/2017 - 12/2017

School of Engineering (ETSE) - University of Valencia - Av. de l'Universitat, s/n, 46100 Burjassot, Spain

Study of the viscosity in simulated fluids using the SPH model. Animation of non-Newtonian fluids. Task related to the Degree Final Project.

Collaboration student

06/2016 - 12/2016

University Research Institute on Robotics and Information and Communication Technologies (IRTIC) - C/ Catedrático José Beltrán, 2, 46980 Paterna, Spain

Researching the relationship between Wi-Fi signal rssi and its possible application in positioning a device in a closed environment. Moreover, I use Python to manage the large amount of data and Java to display the calculations in a graphical interface.

Web developer

09/2014 - 03/2015

Swim Club La Costera – Canals, 46650, Valencia, Spain

Creation of the website. Using Joomla, HTML5 and CSS3.